<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, Splash!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Crew App</string>
    <string name="crash_report_msg">Application Crashed, Report being submitted</string>

	<string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
	<string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
	<string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
	<string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
	<string name="no_data">No data available</string>

    <string name="liteSyncAlertTitle">Lite Sync ?</string>
    <string name="liteSyncAlertMessage">The process will sync data on modules without their relationships. Are you sure to continue?</string>
    <string name="fullSyncAlertTitle">Full Sync ?</string>
    <string name="fullSyncAlertMessage">The process will sync all modules including their relationships. Are you sure to continue?</string>
	<string name="proFeaturePurchaseMessage">Please purchase Pro-Features to enable the required functionality in the application.</string>
    
    
    <string name = "settings_help"><![CDATA[<font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:16px; color:#4B4B4B; font-weight:bold;\">Settings</font><br/><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:14px; color:#666666; font-weight:regular;\">This screen provides you with an interface to connect to your local SugarCRM server using your credentials along with giving different options for importing records.</br></br>You can see the following options:</font><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:12px; color:#828282; font-weight:regular;\"><ul><li>Select Mode<ol><li><b>Online Mode</b>: In this mode the app will make a SOAP call to the server every time you make an action like importing or updating the records in a particular module. So the app will make a connection to the server each time before executing the specific functionality invoked by your action.</li><li>In <b>Offline mode</b>: Once you have made the connection with the server then the records of the selected modules would be saved in the database in the external storage (memory card). In order to get the records of a module the app will make a hit to the database and return the specified results. </li></ol></li><br/><li>No. of records to Import<p>In settings screen you have the option to choose the number of records to import in offline mode. However in online mode this app will get the following records simply by clicking on the Next button in the records list view.</p></li><li>No. of records in list page.<p>You also have the option to choose how many records should be displayed on one page. </p></li></ul></font>]]>
	</string>
	<string name = "import_help"><![CDATA[<font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:16px; color:#4B4B4B; font-weight:bold;\">Import Data</font><br/><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:14px; color:#666666; font-weight:regular;\">On this screen you can start the import process simply by clicking on the Start Import button.<br/></br>The import process may take a few minutes varying according to the number of modules selected and subsequently on the number of records present in each selected module.</font>]]>
	</string>
	<string name = "home_screen_help"><![CDATA[<font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:16px; color:#4B4B4B; font-weight:bold;\">Home Screen</font><br/><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:14px; color:#666666; font-weight:regular;\">On this screen the modules selected in the Configuration Activity are displayed in grid style.<br/><br/>Upon clicking any one of the modules, the records will be displayed in paging style.<br/><br/>In the offline mode, you can synchronize your records to your SugarCRM. The updated records from SugarCRM server will be imported to the app database and the updated records from app database will be exported to the SugarCRM server. </font>]]>
	</string>
	<string name = "module_config_help"><![CDATA[<font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:16px; color:#4B4B4B; font-weight:bold;\">Modules Configuration</font><br/><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:14px; color:#666666; font-weight:regular;\">On this screen a list of modules is displayed for you to select the module you want to view.</font><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:12px; color:#828282; font-weight:regular;\"><ul><li>If in <b>Online Mode</b> then you will be directed next to the home screen to view records of the selected modules in online way by clicking on them.</li><br/><li>If in <b>Offline Mode</b> then you will be directed to the import data screen to import the data of the selected modules and then save to database.</li></ul></font>]]>
	</string>
	<string name = "records_list_help"><![CDATA[<font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:16px; color:#4B4B4B; font-weight:bold;\">Records List</font><br/><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:14px; color:#666666; font-weight:regular;\">On this screen the records of the selected module are displayed in list view in the paging style. Therefore the user can view the Next or Previous record by clicking the respective button.</br></br>The following functionality is also available here:</font><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:12px; color:#828282; font-weight:regular;\"><ul><li>View all existing records</li><li>View only assigned records to this user</li><li>Search for records </li><li>Create a new record</li></ul></font>]]>
	</string>
	<string name = "record_detail_help"><![CDATA[<font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:16px; color:#4B4B4B; font-weight:bold;\">Record Detail</font><br/><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:14px; color:#666666; font-weight:regular;\">On this screen the detail of a specific record selected in the List Activity is displayed with separate field names and their respective values.<br/><br/>You have the option to Edit the record and Save it onto the server in Online Mode and Save it onto local database in Offline Mode.<br></br>At the bottom, there is a list of relationships of the record to the other related modules. </font>]]>
	</string>
	<string name = "new_record_help"><![CDATA[<font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:16px; color:#4B4B4B; font-weight:bold;\">Add/Edit Record</font><br/><br/><font style=\"font-family:Droid Sans; font-size:14px; color:#666666; font-weight:regular;\">On this screen you can enter values into the fields of a particular record and click Save.<br/><br/>You must enter a value into the mandatory (*) fields of the record in order to Save.</font>]]>
	</string>
		
</resources>